University of Arizona Athletics Collection 1913-2011
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Programs, 1916-2011; Series II:
  - Men's Basketball, (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 4), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 4), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Men's Basketball, (3 of 4), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Men's Basketball, (4 of 4), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 4), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 4), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball, (3 of 4), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball, (4 of 4), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 4), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 4), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball, (3 of 4), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball, (4 of 4), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball, (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 4), 1980 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 4), 1980 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball, (3 of 4), 1980 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Men's Basketball, (4 of 4), 1980 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 3), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball, (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 3), 1988 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 3), 1988 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Men's Basketball, (3 of 3), 1988 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 3), 1994 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 3), 1994 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball, (3 of 3), 1994 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 3), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 3), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball, (3 of 3), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 3), 1996 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 3), 1996 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball, (3 of 3), 1996 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 3), 1998 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 3), 1998 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball, (3 of 3), 1998 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball, 2001-2003 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 3), 2009 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 3), 2009 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball, (3 of 3), 2009 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 2), 2010 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 2), 2010 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 2), 2011 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 2), 2011 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Men's Golf; West Region Championship, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Men's Gymnastics, 1967-1979 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Men's Gymnastics, 1973-1980 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Men's Gymnastics, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Men's Track and Field, 1951-1957 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Men's Track and Field, 1958, 1967-1972 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Men's Track and Field, 1981-1995 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Softball, 1988, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Water Polo, 1977, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Women's Basketball, 1981, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Women’s Gymnastics; Pacific 10 Conference Championships, 1989, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Women’s Volleyball, 1982, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Wrestling, 1963-1980 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Media Guides, 1949-2011; Series III:
  This series is arranged alphabetically by sport then chronologically. Media guides document player and team information and statistics for media professionals. Sports with both men’s and women’s teams have individual listings when present. This series contains regular season media guides, as well as post season, and conference championship media guides. Also included is a Men’s Gymnastics’ Press Release Binder that documents the years 1972-1981.
  - Baseball, 1954-1968 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Baseball, 1969-1976 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Baseball, 1977-1992 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Baseball, 1993-1996 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Baseball, 1997-2001 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Baseball, 2002-2004 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Baseball, 2004-2006 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Baseball, 2006-2007 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Baseball, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Baseball, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Cross Country, 1981-1993 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Cross Country, 1995-2007 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Football, 1955-1967 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Football, 1968-1972 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Football, 1972-1974 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Football, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Football, 1975-1977 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Football, 1977-1979 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Football, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Football, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Football, 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Football, 1984, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Football, 1987-1989 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Football, 1989-1991 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Football, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Football, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Football, 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Football, 1996, 1998-1999 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Football, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Football, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Football, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Football, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Football,(2 of 2), 2004 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Football, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Football, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Football, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Football, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Football, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Football; Pac 10 Conference, 1979-1981 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Football; Pac 10 Conference, 1982-1985 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Football; Pac 10 Conference, 1986, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Football; Pac 10 Conference, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Football; Pac 10 Conference, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Football; Pac 10 Conference, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Football; Pac 10 Conference, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Football; Pac 10 Conference, 2004-2005 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Football; Pac 10 Conference, 2006-2007 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Football; Pac 10 Conference, 2007, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Football; Post Season Bowl Games, 1983-1992 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Football; Post Season Bowl Games, (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Football; Post Season Bowl Games, (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Football; Post Season Bowl Games, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Football; Post Season Bowl Games, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Men' Basketball, 1949-1951 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Men' Basketball, 1968-1973 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Men' Basketball, 1973-1976 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Men' Basketball, 1976-1978 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Men' Basketball, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Men' Basketball, 1980-1982 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Men' Basketball, 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Men' Basketball, 1983-1985 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Men' Basketball, 1986-1990 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Men' Basketball, 1990-1993 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Men' Basketball, 1993-1998 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Men' Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Men' Basketball, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Men' Basketball, 2001-2002 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Men' Basketball, 2003-2005 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Men' Basketball, 2005-2006 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Men' Basketball, 2005-2007 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Men' Basketball, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Men' Basketball, 2007-2008 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Men' Basketball, 2008-2009 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Men' Basketball, 2009-2010 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Men' Basketball; Pac 10 Basketball, 1980-1987 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Men' Basketball; Pac 10 Basketball, 1995-2002 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Men' Basketball; Pac 10 Basketball, 2005-2008 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Men' Basketball; Pac 10 Basketball, 2008-2010 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, 1976-1987 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, 1987-1988 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, 1991, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, 1996-1997 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, 1997-1998 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Men' Basketball; Post Season, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Men' Golf, 1967, 1980-2000 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Men' Golf, 2001-2004 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Men' Golf, 2005-2007 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Men' Golf, 2008-2009 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Men' Gymnastics Press Release Binder, (1 of 3), 1972-1981 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Men' Gymnastics Press Release Binder, (2 of 3), 1972-1981 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Men' Gymnastics Press Release Binder, (3 of 3), 1972-1981 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Men' Swimming and Diving, 1975-1998 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Men' Swimming and Diving, 1999-2003 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Men' Swimming and Diving, 2003-2005 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Men' Swimming and Diving, 2005-2007 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Men' Swimming and Diving, 2007-2009 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Men' Tennis, 1978-2001 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Men' Tennis, 2002-2005 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Men' Tennis, 2005-2009 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Softball, 1984-1996 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Softball, 1997-2002 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Softball, 2003-2005 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Softball, 2006-2007 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Softball, 2008-2009 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Softball, 2010 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Softball; 19th Annual NCAA College World Series, May 25-29, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Softball; Pac 10, 2002, 2006-2007 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Track and Field, 1974-1981 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Track and Field, 1982-1989 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Track and Field, 1992-1995 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Track and Field, 1996-2000 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Track and Field, 2001-2004 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Track and Field, 2004-2005 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Track and Field, 2005-2007 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Track and Field, 2007-2009 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Women's Basketball, 1983-1994 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Women's Basketball, 1994-1997 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Women's Basketball, 1997-2000 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball, 2000-2003 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Women's Basketball, 2003-2004 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Women's Basketball, 2004-2005 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Women's Basketball, 2005-2006 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Women's Basketball, 2006-2007 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Women's Basketball, 2007-2008 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Women's Basketball, 2008-2009 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball, 2009-2010 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Women's Golf, 1988-2002 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Women's Golf, 2003-2005 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Women's Golf, 2006-2009 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Women's Gymnastics, 1988, 1992-2001 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Women's Gymnastics, 2002-2007 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Women's Gymnastics, 2007-2010 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Women's Intercollegiate Athletics, 1975, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Women's Soccer, 1995-2001 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Women's Soccer, 2002-2005 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Women's Soccer, 2006-2008 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Women's Swimming and Diving, 1981-1990 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Women's Swimming and Diving, 1999-2003 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Women's Tennis, 1987, 1992-2002 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Women's Tennis, 2003-2007 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Women's Tennis, 2007-2009 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Women's Volleyball, 1982-1992 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Women's Volleyball, 1993-1999 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Women's Volleyball, 2000-2004 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Women's Volleyball, 2004-2007 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Women's Volleyball, 2007-2009 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Other Publications, 1952-2004; Series IV:
  This series is arranged alphabetically. Consists of bulletins, brochures, conference programs, athletic reports and student handbooks.
  - 15th Annual Sports Awards Banquet, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - 39th Annual Senior Awards Banquet, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - 118th Commencement Program, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Arizona Campaign for the Student Athlete, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Arizona Winter Sports, 1962-1963 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Bear Down Bulletin, (1 of 5), 1985-2004 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Bear Down Bulletin, (2 of 5), 1985-2004 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Bear Down Bulletin, (3 of 5), 1985-2004 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Bear Down Bulletin, (4 of 5), 1985-2004 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Bear Down Bulletin, (5 of 5), 1985-2004 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Border Conference Championships, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Border Intercollegiate Athletic Conference Eligibility Rules, 1952-1957 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Brochures, 1951-1977 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Department of Intercollegiate Athletics Fact Book, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Department of Intercollegiate Athletics Policies and Procedures Manual, (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Department of Intercollegiate Athletics Policies and Procedures Manual, (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Eddie Lynch Athletics Pavilion Groundbreaking, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - First Years of the University of Arizona, undated (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Annual Report, (1 of 2), 1995-2004 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Annual Report, (2 of 2), 1995-2004 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics for Women, 1978-1979 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - McKale Memorial Center Dedication Address, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - McKale Memorial Center Dedication Program, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Ninth Annual Western Athletic Conference Spring Championship, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Policy on the Release of Student of Student Information in Compliance with the Family Educational Right and Privacy Act of 1974, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Place to Reach your Goal, undated (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Prospective Student Handbook, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Spring Sports, 1953-1954 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Western Athletic Conference; Basketball Records Book, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - White Paper; Facts and Myths of Intercollegiate Athletics, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Wildcat Club Membership Information, undated (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Wildcat Spirit, undated (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Women’s Intercollegiate Athletics, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 33)
- Ephemera, 1926-1979; Series V:
  Series is arranged alphabetically by type. It contains promotional materials for sporting events; faculty, staff, and press identification cards; student and faulty registration forms; schedules for the men’s basketball team, football team, and other athletic teams; tickets for sporting events, concerts, and social events; and a box of varsity pins.
  - Buttons, Bumper stickers, 1941-1949, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Identification Cards, circa 1952-1970 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Press Passes and Parking Permits, 1937-1979 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Registration Forms, 1954-1955, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Schedules; Basketball, 1938-1977 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Schedules; Football, 1938-1979 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Tickets; Applications, 1946-1976 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Tickets; Baccalaureate Services, Commencement Exercises, 1944-1962 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Tickets; Baseball, 1954-1979 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Tickets; Dances, Banquets, Events, 1952-1979 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Tickets; Desert Mermaids, 1960-1966 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Tickets; Faculty and Staff Season Tickets, 1940-1978 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Tickets; Football, 1930-1979 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Tickets; Intercollegiate Rodeo, 1938-1968 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Tickets; Men’s Basketball, 1946-1979 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Tickets; Performing Acts, 1963-1969 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Tickets; Polo, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Tickets; Season Tickets, 1926-1967 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Tickets; Student Activity Tickets, 1926-1967 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Various Schedules, 1957-1979 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Varsity Pins, undated (Box 45, Item 3)
- Student Handbooks, 1923-1974, 2000; Series VI:
  Series is arranged alphabetically then chronologically. It contains handbooks for University of Arizona students, faculty, and student-athletes. A more complete run of materials is held in the The University of Arizona Main Library and Special Collections Library.
  - Activities Handbooks for Women Students, 1947-1952 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Constitution of Student Body Organization, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - UA Directory of Faculty and Students, 1938-1943 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - UA Directory of Faculty and Students, 1943-1946 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - UA Directory of Faculty and Students, 1946-1947 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - UA Student Handbooks, 1923-1929 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - UA Student Handbooks, 1929-1933 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - UA Student Handbooks, 1933-1939 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - UA Student Handbooks, 1939-1945 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - UA Student Handbooks, 1945-1951 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - UA Student Handbooks, 1951-1954 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - UA Student Handbooks, 1954-1958 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - UA Student Handbooks, 1958-1961 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - UA Student Handbooks, 1966-1970 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - UA Student Handbooks, 1970-1974 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - UA Student-Athlete Handbook, (1 of 2), circa 2000 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - UA Student-Athlete Handbook, (2 of 2), circa 2000 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Scrapbooks, 1918-1999; Series VII:
  Scrapbooks are comprised of newspaper clippings, yearbook clippings, photographs and other memorabilia. The bulk of scrapbooks cover basketball, football, and women’s athletics. Many scrapbooks are in fragile condition. Some scrapbooks were compiled by the athletics department and some were compiled by fans and donated to Athletics.
  - Athletics, 1918-1999; Subseries I:
    - Football/Baseball, 1918-1936 (Item 49)
    - Footballl, 1934 (Item 50)
    - Football, 1935 (Item 51)
    - Football, 1936 (Item 52)
    - Football/Track, 1936-1937 (Item 53)
    - Football, 1937 (Item 54)
    - Football, 1937 (Item 55)
    - Football, 1937-1938 (Item 56)
    - Football/Track, 1938-1939 (Item 57)
    - Football/Track/Men's Basketball, 1939-1941 (Item 58)
    - Football, 1941 (Item 59)
    - Football/Baseball/Men's Basketball, 1946 (Item 60)
    - Football, 1951-1952, 1968 (Item 61)
    - Football, 1951-1952 (Item 62)
    - Football, 1953-1954 (Item 63)
    - Football, 1954-1955 (Item 64)
    - Football, 1955-1956 (Item 65)
    - Football, 1955-1956 (Item 66)
    - Football, 1956-1957 (Item 67)
    - Men's Basketball, 1944-1946 (Item 68)
    - Men's Basketball, circa 1947 (Item 69)
    - Men's Basketball, 1947-1948 (Item 70)
    - Men's Basketball, 1950-1967, 1971 (Item 71)
    - Men's Basketball, 1951-1953 (Item 72)
    - Men's Basketball, 1953-1954, circa 1972 (Item 73)
    - Men's Basketball, 1987-1989 (Item 74)
    - Men's Basketball, 1989-1993 (Item 75)
    - Men's Basketball, 1993-1995 (Item 76)
    - Men's Basketball, 1995-1997 (Item 77)
    - Men's Basketball, 1997 (Item 78)
    - Men's Basketball, 1998-1999 (Item 79)
    - Men's Basketball, 1999 (Item 80)
    - Men's Water Polo, 1975-1980 (Item 81)
    - Men's and Women's Tennis, 1936-1949 (Item 82)
    - Women's Athletics, 1974-1978 (Item 83)
    - Women's Athletics, 1975 (Item 84)
    - Women's Athletics, 1976-1977 (Item 85)
    - Women's Athletics, 1976-1977 (Item 86)
    - Women's Athletics, 1977-1978 (Item 87)
    - Women's Athletics, 1977-1978 (Item 88)
    - Women's Athletics, 1980-1981 (Item 89)
    - Women's Athletics, 1981 (Item 90)
    - Women's Athletics, 1981-1982 (Item 91)
    - Women's Athletics, 1981-1982 (Item 92)
    - Women's Athletics, 1982 (Item 93)
    - Women's Athletics, 1982-1983 (Item 94)
    - Women's Athletics, (1 of 3), 1983 (Item 95)
    - Women's Athletics, (2 of 3), 1983 (Item 96)
    - Women's Athletics, (3 of 3), 1983 (Item 97)
    - Women's Physical Education Majors, 1945-1963 (Item 98)
  - Individuals, 1952-1989; Subseries II
    - Hatcher, Paul, 1952-1957, 1964 (Item 99)
    - Waltke, Grant, 1958-1989 (Item 100)
- Papers of Charles Tribolet, 1949-1975; Series VIII:
  This series maintained the original order in which they were created. Charles “Bumps” Tribolet worked for the University of Arizona Athletics Department for over fifty years. The materials held in this series contains papers that document his years as Graduate Manager (1947), Director of Associated Student Affairs (1947-1962), Appointed Treasure of the Alumni Association (1970), and President of the Collegiate Athletic Business Managers Association (CAMBA) (1960).
  Series contains advertising rates, reports, production costs, general correspondence including materials from the office of President Richard A. Harvill and Robert L. Nugent, request for financial allotments, tour and trip schedules of athletic teams and performing acts, production agreements, contracts, general accounting information, programs, brochures, press releases, and materials documenting University student councils, committees, groups, and services. Also included are materials documenting the Collegiate Athletic Business Managers Association (CABMA).
  - Athletic General, 1956-1968 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Director of Athletics (Mr. McKale), 1956-1960 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Athetics Department, 1966-1970 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Athetics Department, 1971-1972 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Athetics Department, 1972-1973 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Athetics Department, 1973-1974 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Athetics Department, circa 1974 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Events, 1962-1963 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Olympic Fund, U.S., 1963-1971 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - NCAA; Olympic Fund, 1956-1957 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Life passes, 1954-1959 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - NCAA; CABMA, 1957-1968 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - NCAA; CABMA, 1964-1970 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - NCAA; CABMA, 1969-1971 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - NCAA; CABMA, 1949-1950, 1972 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - NCAA; CABMA, 1973-1974 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - NCAA; CABMA, Officers Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 101, Folder 17)